<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sblack dot rocks on S Black (dot) Rocks</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in sblack dot rocks on S Black (dot) Rocks</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sblack.rocks/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More Frequent Notes</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/more-frequent-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 16:58:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/more-frequent-notes/</guid><description>find me notes on blog.sblack.rocks I&amp;rsquo;ve started using evernote and with it discovered Postach.io, which is freak&amp;rsquo;in cool! Now I can publish my evernote notes here blog.sblack.rocks/ without doing anything :)
I still like having a static site on github though, I don&amp;rsquo;t really need anything more. Having control over all the files and (some) control of the content serving is great so I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on deleting this one&amp;hellip; although wagtail has caught my eye as a side project for my (non-existent) free-time ;)</description></item><item><title>Debugging a OAC-BDC Connection</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-oac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:56:29 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-oac/</guid><description>Debugging Oracle Analytics Cloud &amp;amp; Big Data Cloud My job is pretty varied but one thing that stays constant is requests to connect OAC to BDC.
Tail OSA logs Not everyone knows where to find these logs but just run the below command!
tail -f /u01/data/domain/fmw/user_projects/domains/bi/servers/AdminServer/logs/bi.log In our case it reveals some cryptic output&amp;hellip; but it seems that there is a network timeout. That means the issue probably isn&amp;rsquo;t on the OAC side</description></item><item><title>Graphql Oracledb Stand Up Friday Talk</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/graphql-oracledb-stand-up-friday-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:25:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/graphql-oracledb-stand-up-friday-talk/</guid><description>My first developer talk in the books! You can see the recording yourself at this link, or get the presentation and all the materials here unofficialoraclecloudhub.github.io/oracledb-graphql-demo/
This site (hosted from out unofficial cloud-hub GitHub repository) has all the materials I presented in my talk. The GitHub repo that has the code for the site also has everything you need to run the modified GraphsiQL app on a real Oracle Database yourself!</description></item><item><title>Debugging Gatsby Static Site Builder</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-gatsby-static-site-builder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 11:14:21 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-gatsby-static-site-builder/</guid><description>Gatsby JS I love code &amp;amp; I love good documentation so I LOVE a great static-site builder like Hugo, or the super-lightweight static-site scheme oracle learning-library uses. There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of buzz about Gatsby so I decided to give it a go!
I Built a static site with Gatsby js, pictured above &amp;amp; available at https://unofficialoraclecloudhub.github.io/oracledb-graphql-demo/
Building the Site All of the code is available at https://github.com/unofficialoraclecloudhub/oracledb-graphql-demo/tree/master/docs. I used ericwindmill/gatsby-starter-docs as the starting point.</description></item><item><title>Debugging Bash on Windows</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-bash-on-windows/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 11:52:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/debugging-bash-on-windows/</guid><description>TODO:(sblack4) finish links when I get internet
I wrote this on an airplane bach from HQ Debugging Bash on Windows Using the WSL and vscode to debug bash scripts on windows [bash](#TODO:wikipedia on bash) (in this case the windows subsystem for linux), visual studio code, docker these are a few of my favorite things!
is it overkill when your running wsl in a terminal emulator (cmder)
I&amp;rsquo;ve toyed with docker but hadn&amp;rsquo;t seriously used it for work.</description></item><item><title>Recording in Oracle Studios</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 17:36:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</guid><description>Recording in Oracle Studios My team and I had a lot of fun recording demos at Oracle Studios in Redwood Shores, CA!
Check out the green room where @AZaman001 was recording her IOT demo. Not only did the recording staff let us re-record, so we got everything just right, but we got fed too!
The weather was a little chilly - but I do love exploring new places! There were plenty of interesting sights</description></item><item><title>Oracle Moocs</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/oracle-moocs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:27:57 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/oracle-moocs/</guid><description>Oracle Moocs - Join me! Join me on Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Learning Library for a few moocs -
Databases for Developers I loved this course! Chris Saxon has so much energy and enthusiasm for databases, it&amp;rsquo;s infectious. This is a very basic introduction to RDBS and is appropriate for anyone :) Chris also has a fantastic youtube channel - see the intro to the course here
Introduction to PL/SQL See my GitHub repo for the course https://github.</description></item><item><title>My Old Site Sblack Dot Rocks</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:15:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</guid><description>my old site, sblack.rocks is being retired My old static site, was really fun to build (and one of the last things I did in Typescript
which is a FANTASTIC language) but is way more complicated than managing a simple static site like this one, which I can write in Markdown! I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep it on the web, projects like that have nostaligic value. Like looking at old family photos it brings back warm memories and lets me know how much I&amp;rsquo;ve learned since then!</description></item><item><title>Deploying Gh Pages With Hugo</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/deploying-gh-pages-with-hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 14:23:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/deploying-gh-pages-with-hugo/</guid><description>Deploying GitHub Pages with Hugo Learn more about hugo as gohugo.io Create a Hugo site Install Hugo (see chocolatey)
choco install hugo -confirm Follow Directions to install Minimal git submodule add https://github.com/calintat/minimal.git themes/minimal git submodule init git submodule update Set up GitHub Pages Checkout dev branch git checkout -b dev Change master branch to .../sblack.github.io/public From the root of my project (.../sblack.github.io)
git clone -b master https://github.com/sblack4/sblack4.github.io.git public</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:56:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack.rocks/changelog/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World</description></item></channel></rss>