<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>S Black (dot) Rocks</title>
    <link>https://sblack4.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on S Black (dot) Rocks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 11:52:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sblack4.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging Bash on Windows</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/debugging-bash-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 11:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/debugging-bash-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>TODO:(sblack4) finish links when I get internet - I wrote this on an airplane bach from HQ
Debugging Bash on Windows Using the WSL and vscode to debug bash scripts on windows bash (in this case the windows subsystem for linux), visual studio code, docker these are a few of my favorite things!
is it overkill when your running wsl in a terminal emulator (cmder)
I&amp;rsquo;ve toyed with docker but hadn&amp;rsquo;t seriously used it for work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording in Oracle Studios</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 17:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</guid>
      <description>Recording in Oracle Studios My team and I had a lot of fun recording demos at Oracle Studios in Redwood Shores, CA!
Check out the green room where @AZaman001 was recording her IOT demo. Not only did the recording staff let us re-record, so we got everything just right, but we got fed too!
The weather was a little chilly - but I do love exploring new places! There were plenty of interesting sights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Moocs</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/oracle-moocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:27:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/oracle-moocs/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Moocs - Join me! Join me on Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Learning Library for a few moocs -

Databases for Developers I loved this course! Chris Saxon has so much energy and enthusiasm for databases, it&amp;rsquo;s infectious. This is a very basic introduction to RDBS and is appropriate for anyone :) Chris also has a fantastic youtube channel - see the intro to the course here

Introduction to PL/SQL See my GitHub repo for the course https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Old Site Sblack Dot Rocks</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:15:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</guid>
      <description>my old site, sblack.rocks is being retired My old static site, was really fun to build (and one of the last things I did in Typescript - which is a FANTASTIC language) but is way more complicated than managing a simple static site like this one, which I can write in Markdown!
I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep it on the web, projects like that have nostaligic value. Like looking at old family photos it brings back warm memories and lets me know how much I&amp;rsquo;ve learned since then!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 14:54:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> Me I have a baby einstein We&amp;rsquo;re part of a little family  This is all made possible by my first lady &amp;lt;3 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Gh Pages With Hugo</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/deploying-gh-pages-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 14:23:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/deploying-gh-pages-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Deploying GitHub Pages with Hugo Learn more about hugo as gohugo.io Create a Hugo site Install Hugo (see chocolatey)
choco install hugo -confirm  
Follow Directions to install Minimal git submodule add https://github.com/calintat/minimal.git themes/minimal git submodule init git submodule update  
Set up GitHub Pages Checkout dev branch git checkout -b dev  
Change master branch to .../sblack.github.io/public From the root of my project (.../sblack.github.io)
git clone -b master https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:56:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description> Hello World </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>