<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle on S Black (dot) Rocks</title>
    <link>https://sblack4.github.io/tags/oracle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oracle on S Black (dot) Rocks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:25:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sblack4.github.io/tags/oracle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphql Oracledb Stand Up Friday Talk</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/graphql-oracledb-stand-up-friday-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:25:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/graphql-oracledb-stand-up-friday-talk/</guid>
      <description>My first developer talk in the books! You can see the recording yourself at this link, or get the presentation and all the materials here unofficialoraclecloudhub.github.io/oracledb-graphql-demo/
This site (hosted from out unofficial cloud-hub GitHub repository) has all the materials I presented in my talk. The GitHub repo that has the code for the site also has everything you need to run the modified GraphsiQL app on a real Oracle Database yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording in Oracle Studios</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 17:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/recording-in-oracle-studios/</guid>
      <description>Recording in Oracle Studios My team and I had a lot of fun recording demos at Oracle Studios in Redwood Shores, CA!
Check out the green room where @AZaman001 was recording her IOT demo. Not only did the recording staff let us re-record, so we got everything just right, but we got fed too!
The weather was a little chilly - but I do love exploring new places! There were plenty of interesting sights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Moocs</title>
      <link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/oracle-moocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:27:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/oracle-moocs/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Moocs - Join me! Join me on Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Learning Library for a few moocs -

Databases for Developers I loved this course! Chris Saxon has so much energy and enthusiasm for databases, it&amp;rsquo;s infectious. This is a very basic introduction to RDBS and is appropriate for anyone :) Chris also has a fantastic youtube channel - see the intro to the course here

Introduction to PL/SQL See my GitHub repo for the course https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>