<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on S Black (dot) Rocks</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/tags/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on S Black (dot) Rocks</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 16:58:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sblack4.github.io/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More Frequent Notes</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/more-frequent-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 16:58:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/more-frequent-notes/</guid><description>find me notes on blog.sblack.rocks I&amp;rsquo;ve started using evernote and with it discovered Postach.io, which is freak&amp;rsquo;in cool! Now I can publish my evernote notes here blog.sblack.rocks/ without doing anything :)
I still like having a static site on github though, I don&amp;rsquo;t really need anything more. Having control over all the files and (some) control of the content serving is great so I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on deleting this one&amp;hellip; although wagtail has caught my eye as a side project for my (non-existent) free-time ;)</description></item><item><title>Debugging a OAC-BDC Connection</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/debugging-oac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:56:29 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/debugging-oac/</guid><description>Debugging Oracle Analytics Cloud &amp;amp; Big Data Cloud My job is pretty varied but one thing that stays constant is requests to connect OAC to BDC.
Tail OSA logs Not everyone knows where to find these logs but just run the below command!
tail -f /u01/data/domain/fmw/user_projects/domains/bi/servers/AdminServer/logs/bi.log In our case it reveals some cryptic output&amp;hellip; but it seems that there is a network timeout. That means the issue probably isn&amp;rsquo;t on the OAC side</description></item><item><title>Oracle Moocs</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/oracle-moocs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:27:57 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/oracle-moocs/</guid><description>Oracle Moocs - Join me! Join me on Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Learning Library for a few moocs -
Databases for Developers I loved this course! Chris Saxon has so much energy and enthusiasm for databases, it&amp;rsquo;s infectious. This is a very basic introduction to RDBS and is appropriate for anyone :) Chris also has a fantastic youtube channel - see the intro to the course here
Introduction to PL/SQL See my GitHub repo for the course https://github.</description></item><item><title>My Old Site Sblack Dot Rocks</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:15:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/my-old-site-sblack-dot-rocks/</guid><description>my old site, sblack.rocks is being retired My old static site, was really fun to build (and one of the last things I did in Typescript
which is a FANTASTIC language) but is way more complicated than managing a simple static site like this one, which I can write in Markdown! I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep it on the web, projects like that have nostaligic value. Like looking at old family photos it brings back warm memories and lets me know how much I&amp;rsquo;ve learned since then!</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:56:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World</description></item><item><title>sblack dot rocks</title><link>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sblack4.github.io/changelog/</guid><description>welcome to my home on the wild web!
I frequently publish evernote notes too, which automatically end up at blog.sblack.rocks</description></item></channel></rss>